What's up, guys? Miss you guys. How you
doing? Good to see everybody.
>> How you doing?
>> Good. Good. It's good to be back.
>> Um, are you are you surprised you're
here?
>> No. No, I'm not surprised I'm here.
>> Did that get?
>> Not very close, I'd say. I knew I knew
at the bottom of my heart this is where
I wanted to be. Um, and I knew just kind
of from the communication. My I mean my
agents were really doing most of the
communicating right with with the Colts
and stuff like that, but they kept
telling me like they they said we're not
going to let you get out of Indie like
we want you to be a Colts. So I knew um
they wanted me here and I wanted to be
here. So it was an easy decision.
>> Why why was that so important for you to
stay here? Obviously we've seen your pro
progression over the last four years.
What you did with Daniel, the
relationship you've built there. Why was
it so important to hopefully stick
around here for you?
>> Yeah. Um, it's important, you know,
because I think I believe I believe in
what we have going on here. I believe in
our our team. I believe in the players
we have in place, you know. Um, I think
last year or last year in the beginning
of the season, just, you know, that
first half of the season, I think we
truly had something special going and I
know we didn't finish the way we want to
finish. Um, but I think I'm able to look
back to that and look at how we were
playing and know like we can be we can
be the best team in the NFL.
>> You know, you talked last week about
wanting a bigger role within the offense
and with Pitman leaving um that opens
things up more for you. So, it's a
twofold question. One, what' you learn
from Pit about being like the number one
guy and then how much do you think you
can be the number one guy?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, learned so much from
Pit. I, you know, it was a it was truly
great to be teammates with him. He's a
great guy. You know, he took me under
his wing. Um really being, you know,
like when I was a a rookie, you know,
he's just in his third year, but he was
always kind of like that vet presence
even at such a young age. So, he's just
such a mature player, I'd say, in that
sense. And it was great to learn, you
know, how to be a leader, how to be a
captain, how to um lead the room, how
to, you know, basically just just kind
of show everything or show everybody
like the way, you know, the way the the
NFL and and what you got to do to be
successful. So, you know, I'm incredibly
appreciative of having him as a teammate
and not only a teammate, such a great
friend. Um, you know, and I'm excited
for him in Pittsburgh. I think that's
going to be a great opportunity for him
there. Uh, and he ended up in a great
organization. So, I'm excited for him
and his future. But, yeah. No, and then
you said, um, being the number one, um,
you know, that's something I know I I
know I can do. I believe in it and you
know, the opportunities now it's it's
there for me to take it. So, um, you
know, that's going to be something that
I I knew was going to come with getting
this type of contract. And that was the
probably the biggest thing I was excited
about was, you know, not necessarily
like like that, you know, the money and
all that's great, but I but I know with
with that comes like the opportunities
and like the chances to get more balls
thrown to you and just uh affect the
game and more. Al, will the challenge be
for you and the coaching staff to
increase the volume, which it's going to
happen, but still have that big play,
you know, capability in your game cuz
sometimes it's hard to juggle the two.
>> Yeah. Um, I think you can still have the
big play capability. Obviously, like the
big you're you're going to increase the
volume and the big the number of big
plays probably won't won't go up. you
know, you're going to go, if you go from
47 catches to 80 catches, you're not
just going to be it's you're not going
to be a a 21 yards per catch guy at 80
catches. I mean, could be, but that
that's that that would might might break
a record right there. So, um just just
knowing that like people always ask me
about the yards per catch thing. They're
like, "Oh, is this important to you?"
And to to me, I was always like, not
necessarily, cuz I I would rather have I
would take, you know, more catches and
and more yards all day than than having,
you know, less catches and and getting a
higher yards per catch cuz obviously
every catch you catch a slant for for
six yards on third and three. That's
going to bring that that number down,
but that's a that's a huge play in the
game. So, that's the type of stuff I
know I'm going to take on and and and
become, you know, just do things like
that to to help the team win. Um, it's
going to be big.
>> Reggie had was poking his head in here.
What has his uh support and direction
meant to your your development?
>> Yeah, sorry. Who' you say?
>> Reggie.
>> Oh, Reggie. Yeah. No, Reggie. Reggie's
been great. You know, from just from day
one, um, he's always been in my corner
and he's always had my back. Uh, I know
things aren't weren't always going as
smoothly as as they could have been for
me here. Um, and he stuck by me stuck by
with me this whole this whole journey.
Um, and he's been great for me. You
know, I think not only like the on the-
field stuff and the technique and the
the the obvious clear things that he's
going to be working on, but just like
the the mentality and being able to get
through things cuz he he really walked
me through like his career and it's kind
of like like shockingly simil similar
like our numbers and stuff just through
the first few years. But um cuz you know
he always had Marvin in the room and he
would really wasn't you know he was kind
of sitting back in the shadows a little
bit. Obviously, he he he started playing
great ball, but um he was never really
that number one option. So, he kind of
understood and and kind of told me like,
hey, like just be patient. You know, you
just got to keep proving like your
worth, your value. Um showing him that
you can do more things and you'll just
keep building on that. So, I think
that's been something that he's been
great just not only as a coach for me,
but really a mentor and kind of um
helping out my career.
>> It feels like this past year you ran a
more diverse um set of routes. Uh would
you agree with that? Number one and
number two, do you think that helped you
prove something that you already knew
you could do prove to them that much?
>> Yeah. Um yeah, for sure. I think I was
running a lot more a lot more routes
this year, especially like especially
like intermediate stuff, winning at
different levels of the field. Um and
that that's been great. I know that's
something I got to continue just build
on and just continue to prove the more
things you can do, you know, and it
really starts just in practice. like you
get an opportunity,
you know, it might be something where
it's not necessarily like your play, but
some somebody's tired, you jump in there
and you win on something that they're
like, "Oh, yeah, we we normally don't
have you, you know, in the slot doing
this or that." So, um, that's something
that I kind of take pride in. I almost
like feel like I feel like a huge sense
of urgency in practice just on like
especially if I know I'm getting a route
that's not necessarily something I I do
a ton, then it's like, okay, like I I
got to show them here. this be my only
opportunity I get to do this all year.
So if you go out there and and make it
look good, they might be like, "Oh, you
know, I we didn't really think about him
doing this." So yeah, it's something I I
try to work on.
>> What goes through your head personally
this, you know, this last couple days
agreeing to the deal and now signing it
signing. Does it make you kind of think
about more than forward, but just also
back too? Like what what goes through
your head personally?
>> Yeah, for sure. Um, I was actually back
home these past couple days and just
like being back home. It's like the like
reminiscing, you know, like you see like
drive past like the the football field I
played on when I was in like third
grade, you know, like all that type of
stuff. I see. I saw just ran into like
my high school football coaches, stuff
like that. So, um, it's it's it's really
special to kind of look back and that's
something I always I always try to try
to do is cuz I feel like sometimes you
get caught in such like a like a growth
mindset and you and it's like you want
to be you want to be here, but it's like
and sometimes that that's when you can
get kind of down is you're like, man,
like I know I want to be here and I'm
not quite there yet and I need to do
this, do this, do this. Like, but it's
like you got to look at sometimes you
got to look back and look at how far
you've come to, you know, really kind of
I think like,
you know, like give yourself a little
bit of pat on the back sometimes cuz I
know like a lot of people are very very
hard on themselves. I think that's why
like people in in this position. I think
that's why we we get here cuz we're like
perfectionists and we want we just like
are like striving for greatness and
stuff like that. So, it's like a lot
sometimes you got to like look back and
really just appreciate like everything
that's happened and and where you where
you're going.
>> Were you home for the Were you home for
the to make the decision?
>> I was home. Yeah.
>> Was that important to be home with with
your family for for that particular
thing?
>> Um, yeah, for sure. It was just it was
just it's just been me and my dad. My
So, my brothers are actually well, they
don't even live at home, but my my mom
and my mom and brothers are over in
Thailand right now. They're uh my my
brothers are both representing Team USA
for the threeon three basketball. I
think it's like the world championships
or something. So, it's pretty special
cuz they've never had an opportunity to,
you know, they're six years apart. It's
my little brother and older brother. So,
they've never had an opportunity to like
play basketball or any any sports
together. Uh like like a real setting,
you know? So, um it's pretty special. I
think they start on Friday or something.
Is that
>> you're going to be watching games at
like 4 in the morning?
>> Yeah. Hopefully they're recorded. I
think they're recorded on YouTube or
something. So, I'll watch I'll watch
them when I uh when I get up cuz I'm
>> So, along those lines, did you choose
the right sport? I mean, both brothers
are hoopers and
>> Yeah. No, they're you don't want to see
me play basketball. I'm a little They're
a lot taller than me, so they got the
more of the build, but yeah. No, shout
out. Little brother's going to be at uh
Purdue. So, that was another another big
thing. It's like I can't I can't I can't
leave the state when I got my brother
down the road playing some basketball.
It's gonna be his last year of college
basketball, so it'll be special. How
>> was your first going through this free
agency process? There was obviously a
lot of talk about how you were um you
know the most soughtafter wide receiver
on the market. Um you have this major
life-changing decision in front of you
between leaving the team you've been
with for four years or going somewhere
else, you know, rolling the dice and
truly go through free agency. What What
was this whole experience like and was
it any different or similar than what
you thought it might be?
Uh it was it was wild because like I
didn't really realize like the like it
all happens in like
two day period or something like that.
So it's pretty it's pretty crazy how
fast you know you kind of hear like
rumblings through your agent on on oh
this team likes you this team whatever
but then like really come Monday I think
this week is when you can like actually
talk with with somebody on the team. So,
it's like I it seems it seems crazy.
Like, it seems like it just seems like
it's so such a big decision to make in
such a short period of time that um
yeah, it's definitely a little stressful
and overwhelming.
>> How did you deal with that stress and
that pressure? Um
>> yeah. Um,
I mean, for me, I think it wasn't too
bad because I as soon as like I could
tell the Colts were going to do um what
they what they could to keep me here,
then I, you know, cuz I knew I I knew I
wanted to be here, I knew this is like
kind of ultimately the end goal. So, um,
as soon as I knew they were going to be
competitive with what other teams were
were looking at doing, you know, and and
and it wasn't going to have to be like
deciding between, you know, like
somewhere I didn't necessarily want to
be as much, but just a a better
scenario, what not. Like, as soon as I
knew that, then I then it kind of took I
think like the made decision easy,
right, Alex?
>> Alec, how did how did you and Daniel
become so close?
>> Yeah. Um, I don't know cuz it it is it
is shocking like he's only been here I'
I've known him less than a year now and
I feel like you know we're really tight.
So I think just getting together last uh
last off season just I mean he's he's a
great guy. He's a great guy to hang out
with and I think he really stresses just
like you know being together with with
uh the team and that's kind of how I've
always been like I love like like I love
OTA's favorite time of year cuz you have
these little half days and stuff so you
got all this time on your hands like
afternoon and everyone's in town so it's
like try to do something every day
whether we go like play golf or go
>> just do whatever go to the park and
shoot hoops like you know I'm just I'm
just I just like doing stuff and like
hanging out with the boys you know and I
think that's good for like team
camaraderie. Ree and that that's
something that's so important. Um cuz I
always look back to college like how you
know I played at University of
Cincinnati. We had a lot of success
there and we were just so tight. And I I
figured like once you got to the NFL it
was a little different cuz obviously you
know you're not all just hanging out
together and the same age and in college
really that's that's all you got going
on. You got that in class like so you're
just hanging out all the time. But, uh,
I think we started kind of getting back
into that where it's like I'm like
really really close with my teammates.
Like all these guys on the team, like
these are like some of my best friends,
you know, and I think we we'd fight for
each other. We do whatever for each
other. So,
>> you mentioned that when you put pen to
paper, Alec, on a contract like that,
obviously, it's life changing for you
and your family. So, what goes through
your mind? And, um, how gratifying is it
to know that, I don't know, Cincinnati,
you were thinking about playing defense
and then now here you are. on the like
when we say you're the highest paid free
agent receiver in NFL history and you
sign that contract. What goes in your
mind?
>> Yeah. Um it's you know it's definitely
it's definitely a special day. Special
day for me and my family. Um, I think
like
a ton of people have been asking me this
like all all week and stuff and I feel
like I don't know. To me, honestly, like
I really
don't think like I don't think I pay it
that as as much attention as as people
might think I might, you know, like I
think to me it's just like I'm just I
just look at it kind of like dayto-day
and it's like, okay, like what do we got
to do this season? Like I'm going to be
the same person I am, you know? I'm
going to go about things the exact same
way. Um, so yeah, I just I just think
I'm just excited to be back here, be
back in this building. I'm excited we
got Daniel uh a deal a deal done. It
sounds like that that was news today. Um
cuz I'm excited to to just build on what
we had going last year.
>> You mentioned this is where you wanted
to be.
>> Last week you did mention how you'd earn
the right to explore free agency. Was
that just sort of
talk? I mean, you know what I mean? Was
it just part of the part of the process
that you needed to say?
>> Yeah. Um I mean I think
>> yeah it was definitely you know it's
definitely playing playing to the game a
little bit but um also too like I I
didn't really know what was going on
with the quarterback stuff and I I was
telling him from the jump that Daniel
being here was such a big big proponent
for me. Um you know that not and that's
really just like a a credit to Daniel
and and how much I believe in him as the
quarterback. So, I didn't really know,
you know, I don't I don't know all these
different tags and stuff like that going
on. So, I was a little confused for a
little while there and agents kind of
had to and I talked with agents. I
talked with Chris a little bit. They
kind of explained to me like that, you
know, it's going to be okay, like we're
going to get something done cuz I
thought it was like, oh, like any team
can come take him or whatever, you know?
So, I was that that had me just like a
little a little bit stressor for a
while.
>> Why do you believe Daniel as much as you
do? Um, like you said, it's been less
than a year. obviously had some great
times last year. Um has the injury
history, but like all of it. Why do you
still believe that he can be your guy?
>> Yeah, I think um obviously if you just
look at how we're playing just like the
purely like the numbers wise and like
how dominant we were early in the
season. Like that's that's the the big
thing and the kind of obvious thing I
think for everyone to look at. Um but
then I would say really just the just
who he is as a person and how he works
and how he prepares. I think that is
something that gives us like so much
confidence cuz I just know like he's he
is going to be ready to go and he is
going to be prepared as well as he can
for the game and I think obviously the
quarterback is kind of like the leader
and in the like the heart of the team
and um I think we all as a team kind of
feed off that and just like I feel like
uh preparation is confidence, you know,
and I think that allows us to go into
the game feeling confident cuz we just
feel prepared cuz it's like I know this
guy knows exactly what he like
everything he needs to know like going
into this game about the game plan. He
could probably read the game plan to you
like just out of his mind. So, um that I
think that's the biggest